import { Question } from "./QuestionTypes";

export const allQuestions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Where is the oldest continuously inhabited city in the world?",
    answer: "Damascus",
    coordinates: { lat: 33.5138, lng: 36.2765 },
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Where is the highest waterfall in the world?",
    answer: "Angel Falls",
    coordinates: { lat: 5.967, lng: -62.536 },
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "In which city is the headquarters of Volkswagen located?",
    answer: "Wolfsburg",
    coordinates: { lat: 52.4226, lng: 10.7865 },
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Where is the deepest ocean trench in the world?",
    answer: "Mariana Trench",
    coordinates: { lat: 11.35, lng: 142.2 },
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Where is the tallest building in the world?",
    answer: "Burj Khalifa",
    coordinates: { lat: 25.1972, lng: 55.2744 },
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is the highest point on Earth?",
    answer: "Mount Everest",
    coordinates: { lat: 27.9881, lng: 86.925 },
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "In which city is the headquarters of BMW located?",
    answer: "Munich",
    coordinates: { lat: 48.1351, lng: 11.582 },
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "In which city is the global headquarters of Samsung located?",
    answer: "Seoul",
    coordinates: { lat: 37.5665, lng: 126.978 },
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "In which city is the global headquarters of Coca-Cola located?",
    answer: "Atlanta",
    coordinates: { lat: 33.749, lng: -84.388 },
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What is the tallest pyramid in the world?",
    answer: "The Great Pyramid of Giza",
    coordinates: { lat: 29.9792, lng: 31.1342 },
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "Where did the assassination that triggered World War I take place?",
    answer: "Sarajevo",
    coordinates: { lat: 43.8563, lng: 18.4131 },
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      "Where is the site of the first modern Olympic Games held in 1896?",
    answer: "Athens",
    coordinates: { lat: 37.9838, lng: 23.7275 },
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "Where is the location of the first atomic bomb drop in history?",
    answer: "Hiroshima",
    coordinates: { lat: 34.3853, lng: 132.4553 },
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Where was the final of the 2022 FIFA World Cup held?",
    answer: "Lusail Stadium, Lusail",
    coordinates: { lat: 25.416, lng: 51.4886 },
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "Where were the 2020 Summer Olympics held?",
    answer: "Tokyo, Japan",
    coordinates: { lat: 35.6762, lng: 139.6503 },
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "Where was Jesus believed to have been born?",
    answer: "Bethlehem",
    coordinates: { lat: 31.7054, lng: 35.2024 },
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question:
      "In which city are the famous 'Rocky Steps' featured in the movie Rocky located?",
    answer: "Philadelphia, USA",
    coordinates: { lat: 39.9656, lng: -75.1809 },
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question:
      "Which small island was once a federal prison famous for housing notorious criminals like Al Capone?",
    answer: "Alcatraz Island",
    coordinates: { lat: 37.8267, lng: -122.423 },
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "Where was the Prophet Muhammad born?",
    answer: "Mecca",
    coordinates: { lat: 21.3891, lng: 39.8579 },
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "Where is the Mona Lisa displayed?",
    answer: "Louvre Museum, Paris",
    coordinates: { lat: 48.8606, lng: 2.3376 },
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question:
      "In which city is Shakespeare's tragedy about Romeo and Juliet set?",
    answer: "Verona",
    coordinates: { lat: 45.4384, lng: 10.9916 },
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "Where is the headquarters of the Red Cross located?",
    answer: "Geneva",
    coordinates: { lat: 46.2262, lng: 6.1432 },
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "Where was the ancient city of Troy located?",
    answer: "Hisarlik",
    coordinates: { lat: 39.9578, lng: 26.2389 },
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "Where were the 2022 Winter Olympics held?",
    answer: "Beijing",
    coordinates: { lat: 39.9042, lng: 116.4074 },
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "Where did the D-Day landings of World War II take place?",
    answer: "Normandy",
    coordinates: { lat: 49.4144, lng: -0.8322 },
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "Where did the world's worst nuclear disaster occur in 1986?",
    answer: "Chernobyl Nuclear Power Plant",
    coordinates: { lat: 51.389, lng: 30.0994 },
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question:
      "Where is the impact site of the asteroid believed to have caused the extinction of the dinosaurs?",
    answer: "Chicxulub crater, Yucatán",
    coordinates: { lat: 21.4, lng: -89.5 },
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "Where is the only Grand Slam tennis tournament played on grass?",
    answer: "Wimbledon, London",
    coordinates: { lat: 51.4343, lng: -0.214 },
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question:
      "In which city did Muhammad Ali fight George Foreman in the legendary 'Rumble in the Jungle' in 1974?",
    answer: "Kinshasa",
    coordinates: { lat: -4.4419, lng: 15.2663 },
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question:
      "At which mountain pass did 300 Spartans fight the Persian army in 480 BC?",
    answer: "Thermopylae",
    coordinates: { lat: 38.7969, lng: 22.5361 },
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    question:
      "After which battle did German forces begin a major retreat on the Eastern Front during World War II?",
    answer: "Battle of Stalingrad",
    coordinates: { lat: 48.708, lng: 44.5133 },
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    question:
      "Where did the largest tank battle in history occur during World War II?",
    answer: "Kursk",
    coordinates: { lat: 51.73, lng: 36.192 },
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question:
      "Which ancient city was buried under volcanic ash after the eruption of Mount Vesuvius in 79 AD?",
    answer: "Pompeii",
    coordinates: { lat: 40.7497, lng: 14.4869 },
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question:
      "On which island did Christopher Columbus first set foot during his 1492 voyage?",
    answer: "San Salvador Island",
    coordinates: { lat: 24.0583, lng: -74.535 },
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    question: "Where does the Pope officially reside?",
    answer: "Vatican City",
    coordinates: { lat: 41.9029, lng: 12.4534 },
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    question:
      "Which islands did Charles Darwin study that were key to his theory of evolution?",
    answer: "Galápagos Islands",
    coordinates: { lat: -0.9538, lng: -90.9656 },
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question:
      "In which city is the Formula 1 race held entirely on public streets?",
    answer: "Monaco",
    coordinates: { lat: 43.7336, lng: 7.4206 },
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    question:
      "Which city did the Ottomans capture in 1453, marking the fall of the Byzantine Empire?",
    answer: "Constantinople (Istanbul)",
    coordinates: { lat: 41.0082, lng: 28.9784 },
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    question:
      "At which archaeological site was the Minotaur said to live in a labyrinth?",
    answer: "Knossos, Crete",
    coordinates: { lat: 35.2989, lng: 25.1638 },
  },
  {
    id: 40,
    question:
      "Near which modern-day city was the ancient city of Carthage located?",
    answer: "Tunis",
    coordinates: { lat: 36.8529, lng: 10.3239 },
  },
  {
    id: 41,
    question:
      "Which city did Alexander the Great found and name after himself?",
    answer: "Alexandria",
    coordinates: { lat: 31.2001, lng: 29.9187 },
  },
  {
    id: 42,
    question: "In which city is the headquarters of Spotify located?",
    answer: "Stockholm",
    coordinates: { lat: 59.3293, lng: 18.0686 },
  },
  {
    id: 43,
    question:
      "In which city is the headquarters of the United Nations located?",
    answer: "New York City",
    coordinates: { lat: 40.748, lng: -73.968 },
  },
  {
    id: 44,
    question:
      "In which city was U.S. President John F. Kennedy assassinated in 1963?",
    answer: "Dallas",
    coordinates: { lat: 32.7767, lng: -96.797 },
  },
  {
    id: 45,
    question: "Near which city is the Terracotta Army located?",
    answer: "Xi'an",
    coordinates: { lat: 34.3847, lng: 109.2785 },
  },
  {
    id: 46,
    question:
      "At which place was the treaty officially ending World War I signed in 1919?",
    answer: "Palace of Versailles",
    coordinates: { lat: 48.8049, lng: 2.1204 },
  },
  {
    id: 47,
    question:
      "At which place did the Japanese attack in 1941 that prompted the United States to enter World War II?",
    answer: "Pearl Harbor",
    coordinates: { lat: 21.3649, lng: -157.95 },
  },
  {
    id: 48,
    question:
      "In which city are the annual Academy Awards, also known as the Oscars, presented?",
    answer: "Los Angeles",
    coordinates: { lat: 34.102, lng: -118.34 },
  },
  {
    id: 49,
    question: "In which city were the members of The Beatles born?",
    answer: "Liverpool",
    coordinates: { lat: 53.4084, lng: -2.9916 },
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    question: "In which city was composer Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart born?",
    answer: "Salzburg",
    coordinates: { lat: 47.8095, lng: 13.055 },
  },
];
